fashnvia.com 2010-06-28

# Fashnvia.com - Shop latest Mens, Womens Fashion (Apparel, Footwear, Accessories) & Brand Vouchers - Online Fashion Shopping Store for India

Last Modified on: 28 August 2009

At FASHNVIA.com we recognize that Privacy is extremely important and we are committed to protecting the Privacy of all FASHNVIA.com members. FASHNVIA.com's goal is to provide a highly valuable online fashion shopping platform for our members that will help them to purchase latest, exciting branded product range and vouchers at attractive discounted prices. 

This Privacy Policy is designed to help you learn more about the personal information we collect, who we might share it with, and how we protect it. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the **FASHNVIA.com Terms of Use**. Your use of the FASHNVIA.com services and any personal information you provide in FASHNVIA.com during registration or while updating your profile remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our **Terms of Use**. 

Please note that certain features of the FASHNVIA.com portal allow you to publish opinions, discoveries, suggestions, comments, photos, pictures, videos & other content or files. The information voluntarily published under these categories will be considered as published information and shall not be falling within the purview of this Privacy Policy. 

We collect certain information during your visit to and use of FASHNVIA.com. The information collected are of the following types: 

•  Information provided by you during registration and profile updation in FASHNVIA.com 

•  Information provided by you when you invite your friends to join FASHNVIA.com 

FASHNVIA.com members can invite their friends to join FASHNVIA.com. We store and use the names and email addresses of Friends that Members provide us in order to send Join FASHNVIA.com invitations to their Friends and, if necessary, to remind Members' Friends that they have been invited to Join FASHNVIA.com. 

•  Information collected through web server logs 

When you use FASHNVIA.com services, for example the moment you log into FASHNVIA.com, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends. These server logs may include information such as where the Member is coming from (internet protocol address), very precise date and time of the request, feature or service that was requested, protocol used to request the page, referrer URL, information about the operating system used by the visitor, the web browser used by the visitor etc. 

•  Information collected by third parties 

In addition we may tie up with third parties such as advertisers who may also collect certain information from you via their campaigns (when you voluntarily provide your information to them). These third parties may use the information to promote their product and services, to measure the efficiency of ads, tracking user trends, etc 

FASHNVIA.com does not make any representations or warranties regarding the use / collection of information collected by such third parties. The collection and use of such information by the third parties is not covered by the present Privacy Policy and the users are requested to read the respective privacy policies of these third parties. Infact the privacy polices of these third parties may differ from our Privacy Policy. 

**How your Information is used**

The information provided to FASHNVIA.com by you is used to provide you with our services as well as maintain your account with us. 

All information that you provide during registration (except for your personal email id, account password) forms part of your Profile in FASHNVIA.com.

**Disclosure of your personal information to third parties**

FASHNVIA.com will never disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any third party, except if required to do so by law or in the good faith that such action is necessary to confirm to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on FASHNVIA.com, protect and defend the rights or property of FASHNVIA.com or act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of FASHNVIA.com members. 

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures. 

Account Passwords are encrypted and hence nobody including FASHNVIA.com team can view them. 

We implement technology and procedures to try to make sure that external parties cannot access or modify users' personal information on our servers. 

We restrict access to personal information to FASHNVIA employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to FASHNVIA.com and you do so at your own risk. This is also not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

**Data Integrity**

We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our Members to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**Notification of changes:**

We reserve the right at any time to: change the terms of this Privacy Policy; change the Services, including eliminating or modifying any or all of the content / features in FASHNVIA.com; change/charge fees for use of FASHNVIA.com Services. 

FASHNVIA.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any changes. Your use of the FASHNVIA.com Portal following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. Be sure to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure your familiarity with the most current version. You will always be able to tell when the version was last updated by checking the ‘Last Revised' date in the header of this Privacy Policy.
